<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- For current Unix time at UTC, use this command: date -u +%s or go to http://www.unixtimestamp.com/-->
<!-- Of course, this is just a XML file so there is no DOCTYPE -->
<blogs xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="blog.xsd">
	<blog>
		<time>1254903072</time>
		<title>I don't know</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>The biggest problem with blogging is that it makes you think you have an audience, and most of the time you expect your audience to listen to your intelligent ramblings. Thus, a lack of audience is even more enforcing of the thought that you actually, really have an audience and it is intelligent too. I have personally tried hard to overcome this inherent inference, but whenever I do it successfully, I lose interest in writing any further.</p>
			<p>So this time, I will let myself a little loose.</p>
			<p>Here is the thing. I feel I am a little lost. I feel a little agitated and confused (or vice-versa). I feel I have grown more and more frustrated by India. I believe that it is because I am not entirely satisfied currently, and that an agitated and confused person tries to find fault at his/her home. I feel like I should catch somebody by his/her shoulders and shake it vigorously. I have stuff to do and no body to ask to. I feel I need to find a "way", but I am all on my own. I guess I am growing up! - Only ten years later, God! -<p>
			<p>I need to hold this situation tight! And start acting! Blindly! The worst that can happen to me is that I will end up killing some people. That doesn't seem so bad! :D Don't you think you deserve to die, asshole!</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1253532147</time>
		<title>Recurring thought</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>I am writing this again. There is no particular reason for me to write, except that I am bored and a little clueless. I don’t particularly, still, miss college days - does that make me crazy? I do miss all the stuff I should have done but I ultimately didn’t. But, I guess, I did what I could do. I miss stuff that I wish I was doing, but I did what I could do. Is that the only reason for my unhappiness? This unrealistic disconnect?</p>
			<p>I have some money now. It is nice to earn something, and as I saw in my student days, it is nice to spend something. It is just nice. Yet there is an emptiness. I am still longing for stuff I cannot have. You know what I mean!</p>
			<p>Do I long for India? Not at all! I just don’t particularly like Germany. It could have been a better place had I been more normal in the start. I missed umpteen chances to meet new people, have an affair. Do I want to have a girlfriend? I don’t think so, though having one will probably do me some good. I long for an affair. I long for that emptiness which comes when know what you want.</p>
			<p>Once again, do I long for India? Not at all! It is filled with people who are still smug about their CPI. It is filled with people who would rather ridicule me for what I had and they couldn’t. Only yesterday some chump went on and on about IITans - called me a nerd in 1st sentence - about how he was “too little in front of giants like me”. I had to ask him to stop mentioning this word in front me, and then he went ahead to meet someone else. Cool dude! Asshole!! India is filled with people like him. Ignorant and in general not so nice people.</p>
			<p>I don’t mean to say that Germans are any different. No, absolutely not! They aren’t. Half of them are skin deep racist. And I say that while I have discounted so many other incidents as  “human nature”. They are also mostly ignorant, and in general not so nice people. <i>That</i> is not the difference! The difference is that I don’t really care about Germans! I know that I WILL leave Germany some time in future, once and for all! But what to do in India? Where will I go if I go to India? Stuck in Gurgaon or Pune? Job is not important! How will I survive crazy people? Why won’t I hit them (beside me being non-aggressive)? No sir! I will stay in a generally more predictable place.</p>
			<p>The tortoise reminds me of myself. Shut-up!</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1243185127</time>
		<title>Chapter 1.1 manuscript</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>But no one was there. </p>
			<p>Ravi comes back to his bed and falls like a dead log. Asleep, now he is devoid of any dreams.</p>
			<p align="center"><strong>II</strong></p>
			<p>It has snowed last night. At 10 o’clock Ravi is still clumsy and in bed. Heater is full on and he is naked under a quilt, coughing and sweating at the same time. Reeky dank branches of the leafless tree outside his closed window are dripping with melted snow. Sun is far from visible, yet there is a light orange aura everywhere outside - street lights are still on. Further buildings are not visible through the mist. Good thing nothing of the room is visible from outside either, Ravi thinks.</p>
			<p>He is not entirely happy about it. He should have had more money for new window curtains. As for now, he is dependent on courtsey of people living in the front building. Or may be not.</p>
			<p>His friend didn’t come. Another night passed. Afterall, when you have nothing to do, you get tired easily. And a good dreamless sleep is only that much helpful.</p>
			<p>Ravi dreams about Suresh. He thinks how well Suresh understands him. Of course Suresh is doing a job now. Probably going to get married in coming months, he will have even less time to chit-chat with Ravi. After Ravi left to Germany, he has been having a lot of trouble adjusting. Everything is difference here. Twenty five years of prepartion are going to waste, he thinks. He should be back. But even back home is not easy. It is not the land, but his preparation which is foreign. Foreign and strange. He wonders if his lethargy has a reason beside himself. None of his friends are like Suresh, may be? He knows why he did what he did. But it doesn’t quite feel right.</p>
			<p>Strange thoughts come to his mind. Ravi rolls over to the other side of the bed and hits the wodden wall, making a lot of noise.</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
	    <time>1231951016</time>
	    <title>About not being able to change</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/peanuts_blanket2.gif" alt="2" /><br />
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/peanuts_blanket5.gif" alt="4" /><br />
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/peanuts_blanket...last.gif" alt="last" />
			</p>
			<p>
			Peanuts: &copy; United Feature Syndicate
			</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1229819503</time>
		<title>Chapter 1 manuscript</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p align="center"><strong>I</strong></p>
			<p>It is night. There could have been moonlight, but Ravi never noticed it. You cannot notice it in a well lit house. Most hopefully it wasn’t there in the first place.</p>
			<p>We see a house with glass walls. It looks like a dining room. A lot of people are standing in a whirling line outside the door. It is just the door for dining room, not the house. People are outside in the garden. On a closer look it looks like some party was going on - there are tables with upside down glasses – but no food. In the end of the line is Ravi, who was quietly standing until now, when he starts to walk towards the door and successfully enters too! No one stops him, he goes inside, going round the dining table following exactly the path the whole line is supposed to follow, and at the end is a big black box – about the same size of his own – laying rest on the wall. No one’s in the dining room except Ravi, some people are in the other room visible through the open connecting door. Yes! There is a party going on in the next room – a lot of old people dressed in good dark colored clothes.</p>
			<p>Ravi stands there for several minutes, hopefully contemplating, but we won’t know – we are not Ravi. He gets out and joins the now yet longer line in the end. Standing right there is his old friend Suresh. A conversation begins,</p>
			<p>“Hey! Exciting stuff! It really is! I was just inside looking at the machine when it hit me…”</p>
			<p>Suresh begins to smile, as if he knows where the conversation is going…</p>
			<p>“… It hit me… that… I mean… these guys have got a minimum time below which they don’t calculate anything! The whole program runs in chunks of time – I mean they really have a small delta time and all, they have gone to great lengths.”</p>
			<p>“Yeah, I know!”</p>
			<p>“I was just thinking, you know, that suppose this program runs for a long time, I mean, for several…”</p>
			<p>“It won’t.”</p>
			<p>“Yes! I know! I was just saying that suppose this program runs for several hundred, no million, or billion…”</p>
			<p>Suresh is smiling again. Ravi continues without a stop. Meanwhile the line has already started moving, and some people are already inside the room.</p>
			<p>“… I mean I know it won’t, but imagine it runs for billions of years, would they…”</p>
			<p>A sharp noise is heard and Ravi wakes up. It was supposed to be a masterpiece of a dream but as always someone has interrupted, as evidenced with this annoying extra loud door bell. Ravi quickly assumes that a friend he was expecting has arrived a night earlier, and he mechanically presses the button to open the door.</p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1228383931</time>
		<title>Another brick in the wall</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p><a href="http://xkcd.com/386/">http://xkcd.com/386/</a></p>
			<p>Sometime in the past, something wrong happened to me. Something evil. Now I don’t get angry when someone is wrong on the internet. Or if I do, I don’t waste time telling them the eternal truth.</p>
			<p>But when someone is wrong in <i>real life</i>, I am aggravated! This is totally unacceptable!</p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1223405788</time>
		<title>Eco 101 - Introduction to Economics</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>Now I am living in a home - four Indians, including me. Now, I am a temporary “guest” living in my friend’s room, and I don’t know the “house rules”. (Btw, I am really glad that he is letting me stay, stupid moron that I am) (Really! He tolerates me a lot which is not something most people do before realising I am a stupid moron. ... wait! Well, still!)</p>
			<p>So, I was saying that I don’t know the house rules, like where should one throw the garbage away. And I am telling you, last time I felt it was too dirty so asked my room-mate where it is thrown, and then he threw it himself, and another guy thanked me for that while adding it was him who threw it last time.</p>
			<p>Now it’s been more than 10 days since then, and two garbage packs are full, in the kitchen. I am not going outside at all these days otherwise I would have thrown it myself.</p>
			<p>So, what happened today? I came across <a href="http://www.econlib.org/library/Enc/TragedyoftheCommons.html">this</a>. That’s all. It is a great website and I recommend it to all of you. It is a pity that as a society whose basis is education (well, partially, at least!), we don’t learn much economics. It should be a compulsory course - micro economics in high-school, and macro economics in inter. Or vice-versa.</p>
			<p>That’s it. And “it has been so long that you would be thinking I am dead, so I am posting this! :)”.</p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1214311840</time>
		<title>The geese and the tortoise</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>Once upon a time there lived a pair of geese and a tortoise all three of whom were great friends. One day they faced a huge drought and the lake in which they lived was drying up. They decided to leave the lake and look for a new lake. But the tortoise could not fly. So the geese thought of a plan, where by the tortoise would have to hold a piece of stick by its mouth which would be carried by the two geese. The only condition was that the tortoise should not speak or it will fall from the stick to death. The tortoise agreed to be silent.</p>
			<p>But on seeing this strange arrangement, people on the way started laughing at the tortoise. Unable to control his anxiety, he spoke out “What are they laughing about?”, and so fell to his death. If he had kept quiet he could have saved his own life.</p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1213655654</time>
		<title>Feed added</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>A RDF feed has been added, which you can add in your favorite news feed reader. I personally use Google Reader - but frankly, it sucks! (I was playing with the blog XML file yesterday, and for some reason, Google Reader has saved a cache of it and won’t update it at all! Even if I delete the feed and re-add it</p>
			<p>Google is only good for one thing: searching. It sucks on everything other ground.</p>
			<p>Anyway...</p>
			<p>The only “modern” thing left is ‘tagging’. That <em>should</em> take a long time.</p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1212835224</time>
		<title>1984</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<h2 style="text-align: center;">IGNORANCE IS STRENGTH</h2>
			<h2 style="text-align: center;">Power is not a means; it is an end.</h2>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1211756224</time>
		<title>Hate</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>The title says it all, doesn’t it.</p>
			<p>I mean, how hard it is to take a picture? Looking for beauty in something where it doesn’t exist.</p>
			<p>Art is personal - that is how it is supposed to be. Appreciators of art are appreciating their own conceptions. Unless you consider wittiness as art too.</p>
			<div style="margin-left: 30%; margin-right: 30%;">
				<p style="text-align: left;">
					Now look at them yo-yo's that's the way you do it<br />
					You play the guitar on the MTV<br />
					That ain't workin' that's the way you do it<br />
					Money for nothin' and chicks for free<br />
					Now that ain't workin' that's the way you do it<br />
					Lemme tell ya them guys ain't dumb<br />
					Maybe get a blister on your little finger<br />
					Maybe get a blister on your thumb<br />
					<br />
					We gotta install microwave ovens<br />
					Custom kitchen deliveries<br />
					We gotta move these refrigerators<br />
					We gotta move these colour TV's<br />
					<br />
					See the little faggot with the earring and the makeup<br />
					Yeah buddy that's his own hair<br />
					That little faggot got his own jet airplane<br />
					That little faggot he's a millionaire<br />
					<br />
					We gotta install microwave ovens<br />
					Custom kitchens deliveries<br />
					We gotta move these refrigerators<br />
					We gotta move these colour TV's<br />
					<br />
					I shoulda learned to play the guitar<br />
					I shoulda learned to play them drums<br />
					Look at that mama, she got it stickin' in the camera<br />
					Man we could have some fun<br />
					And he's up there, what's that? Hawaiian noises?<br />
					Bangin' on the bongoes like a chimpanzee<br />
					That ain't workin' that's the way you do it<br />
					Get your money for nothin' get your chicks for free<br />
					<br />
					We gotta install microwave ovens<br />
					Custom kitchen deliveries<br />
					We gotta move these refrigerators<br />
					We gotta move these colour TV's, Lord<br />
					<br />
					Now that ain't workin' that's the way you do it<br />
					You play the guitar on the MTV<br />
					That ain't workin' that's the way you do it<br />
					Money for nothin' and your chicks for free<br />
					Money for nothin' and chicks for free
				</p>
				<p style="text-align: right;">&mdash; Dire Straits</p>
			</div>
			<p style="font-size: small;"><em>Update (07/JUN/08): Added lyrics</em></p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1211458878</time>
		<title>ThinkPad 560X - a quest to waste more time</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>Hi!</p>
			<p>Some days ago I bought a IBM ThinkPad 560X. Made in UK with all its glory, it is really tough, since I have already dropped it twice from my bed and it is still running. It comes with 231 MHz Intel Mobile Pentium MMX, and stock 32 MB ram. In 1997, it would have costed more than a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lakh">lakh</a> in India, and I bought it in 25 &euro; :-)</p>
			<p>Who would have thought!</p>
			<p>I got it at a Flohmarkt (en: flow market). It came with a port-extension, a cd drive and a floppy drive. CD drive would have needed a 10V-1000mA adapter, in case it was working. If I remember correctly, the guy who sold me all the stuff had a similar adapter but didn’t give it to me since “it was not needed”.</p>
			<p><a href="http://www.thinkwiki.org/wiki/Category:560X">560X</a> comes with InfraRed port, a USB 1.1 (or is it 1?) port, a serial port, a parallel port and 2 Type II PCMCIA card slots. There is no ethernet card, though. Windows 98 SE was already installed on it, along with Microsoft Office 97, acrobat reader etc. On a general look I found that the guy did a good job of “cleaning” it - except removing the user/password thing (for those who don’t know, in Windows 98, when asked for password one can press ‘Cancel’ and login as administrator). Computer was definitely in use until 2001-2002. All the disks (total of 4 GB) were de-fragmented and the whole Windows 98 installation disk along with a set of drivers were present on a partition. In a sweeping move of ignorance I delete all of them - only to know later that I needed to install USB drivers from those directories.</p>
			<p>Until now I hadn’t figured out that one flat strange looking thing was actually a working floppy drive.</p>
			<p>The day I did, I installed generic USB drivers from internet (sorry, cannot find links right now). From that time onwards it became easy. I bought a PCMCIA USB adapter in 15 &euro; and was able to connect my 300 GB Maxtor 3200 HD. Although I had heard a lot that Maxtor doesn’t provide any drivers for Windows 98, it worked (and still works) flawlessly with generic USB drivers. I must admit, though, that Maxtor 3200 doesn’t have backward compatibility with USB 1.1.</p>
			<p>Then it became a little easier. I installed Winamp 5 (classic skin) and was able to play mp3s. The computer is fast enough to play MPEGs with small resolution, but failed miserably while playing DivX movies. Ok, may be not miserably, but still a lot jerky. I tested with Vlc and Media Player Classic (MPC). MPlayer was able to play audios, but would crash while trying to play videos.</p>
			<p>So I decided to install Gentoo - super optimized Linux operating system. Actually, Vlc was able to play a lot of movies, albeit a lot jerky. That’s what gave me the idea to see the affect of optimization.</p>
			<p>After looking through almost all the Stuttgart and eBay and Craiglist, I was unable to find an adapter for the external CD drive. After much reseach, some one at <a href="http://www.linuxquestions.org">LinuxQuestions.org</a> told me about Loadlin. For those who don’t know, using Loadlin you can boot into Linux environment directly from DOS. Voila! Within no time I had installed Damn Small Linux on the 500 MB partition.</p>
			<p>I must now say something about Damn Small Linux. It is awesome - and it has the most worthless support system. They have a forum on which no one is able to post anything - it says “permission denied” for <em>every fucking thing</em>. They have a wiki where you can post your questions if forum is not working - and since forum is working for everyone except you, no one is on wiki to reply. No one except people who have posted “forum is not working for me”. They don’t have an IRC channel, or mailing-list of any sort.</p>
			<p>Did I say that the whole web page of Damn Small Linux has absolutely no other link to contact them? I know they are doing cool things there, but the whole web page is full with shear arrogance and pleas for donation. I would have gladly donated some money if I were able to do anything other than downloading the ISO and fighting my way to run it using Loadlin. And the iso itself is loaded on ibiblio.org - so no points to DSL.</p>
			<p>Stuck with DSL and broken availability of GCC on it, I tried to use GRML. GRML doesn’t work on 32 MB ram.</p>
			<p>Then I tried Debian Woody which can be booted using floppy. I couldn’t fathom the courage to update it to Sarge without internet connection, though. So I was stuck again.</p>
			<p>Then, after much web-diving, I found out that Slackware, as late as version 11.0, had boot disks (they don’t have now). Hey! This is what I wanted! A real system to work on (unlike DSL which comes with BusyBox, and unlike DSL-N, which won’t boot at all. Did I tell you I was unable to get any help?)</p>
			<p>I also tried to boot in Slackware 12.1 using Loadlin. And also Debian Sarge, but in both cases I was unable to. Documentation for doing it is so scarce and whatever there is, well, is just farce. Really - there are tutorials that say “you can just give <tt>loadlin.exe kernel kerneloptions</tt>” to run this and that - something that is from the first line of loadlin help.</p>
			<p>Anyway, I had to burn 4 floppies: boot.img, install.1, install.2 and pcmcia.dsk. The fourth disk was important so that I could use my PCMCIA USB adapter to connect to the big external HD I mentioned earlier. After that it was easy. I download the Slackware-11.0 installation DVD on external hard disk, mounted it, and insalled everything from it (Slackware setup has options for this purpose). I installed a minimal Slackware system (only the required things), and gcc. After which I compiled kernel 2.4.36.4 - ATTENTION: Only alsa 1.0.8 works with 2.4 kernel series. Then I compiled a lot of things:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>vim</li>
				<li>xvid</li>
				<li>x264</li>
				<li>mplayer</li>
				<li>zsh</li>
				<li>rxvt-unicode</li>
				<li>imagemagick</li>
				<li>jwm</li>
				<li>etc...</li>
			</ul>
			<p>All with <tt>CFLAGS="-O2 -march=pentium-mmx -mtune=pentium-mmx"</tt> and <tt>CXXFLAGS=$CFLAGS</tt>. If anyone of you want these packages, you can mail me at the email address given at the end of this webpage, and I will mail/upload it for you.</p>
			<p>One thing that I learned after all this is that installing Gentoo would have been the worst thing. It would have taken weeks to get a working system. Currently, the only system hungry program that I have not compiled myself is X, and that just makes a lot of sense :-)</p>
			<p>Final result? The computer is quite responsive and I am able to watch many DivX movies (but not HD content, ofcourse). For those movies which are still a little jerky, I use lowres option in mplayer.</p>
			<p>Well, so much for now, will update if any more problems creep in :-)</p>
			<p>Meanwhile, I am extremely thankful to guys at <a href="http://forums.gentoo.org">Gentoo Forums</a> and <a href="http://www.linuxquestions.org">LinuxQuestions.org</a> who helped me at almost every step.</p>
			<p>
				<strong>UPDATE:</strong><br />
				<a href="http://cubicledenizen.blogspot.com/2008/04/no-cd-no-network-no-floppy-operating_09.html">This blog deals with loading Slackware using Loadlin extensively.</a>
			</p>
			<div style="font-size: small;">
				<p>References:</p>
				<ol>
					<li>http://www.damnsmalllinux.org/</li>
					<li>http://home.comcast.net/~fbui/Linux-on-TP560x.html</li>
					<li>http://www.damnsmalllinux.org/wiki/index.php/Loadlin_Install</li>
					<li>http://www.slackware.com/faq/do_faq.php?faq=installation#1</li>
					<li>http://thalreit.de/twiki/bin/view/UsingUNIX/DebianThinkpad560</li>
				</ol>
			</div>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1208993402</time>
		<title>PHP 4 and XML parsing (update)</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>XML parsing with PHP 4 is dodgy at best. Otherwise it is broken. Thanks to guys at <a href="http://www.programmingtalk.com/">ProgrammingTalk</a> who helped me in successfully parsing my blog in XML while avoiding the untimely death of SAX parser. I could have moved to an another server hosting PHP 5... but for now everything seems to work as it should, so I have delayed that plan.</p>
			<p>I also changed the current CSS style-sheet for the blog, and I think now it looks very nice - and so it will stay just like this for quite some time. Although, I would say, the blue panel is quite ugly and doesn’t really fit, for now I have left it. The <em>major changes</em> are addition of “More” link, so that this page never gets too big (a calendar and a tag system is still left - will add them in time) and the reporting format of time of comments (“2 seconds ago” etc.).</p>
			<p>I am happy for now :)</p>
			<p><em>Walled Garden Near Ghat - tested / OK from Lynx and w3m.</em></p>
			<p><a href="http://walledgardennearghat.com/other_programs.html">Source code is here.</a></p>
			<p style="font-size: small;"><em>Update (07/JUN/08): Added link to source code.</em></p>]]>
		</text>
	</blog>
	<blog>
		<time>1207155573</time>
		<title>PHP 4 and XML parsing</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>Finally!</p>
			<p><em>... Update coming ...</em></p>
			<p>And by the way: <a href="http://jeremy.zawodny.com/i/pony.jpg">No, you can’t have a pony!</a></p>
			<!-- p style="text-align: center;"><img src="images/pony.jpg" alt="no pony" /></p -->
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1206612274</time>
	    <title>Test</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>I am testing my string sanitization. Everyone is welcome to break it (please don’t break the whole website, though :( I am a good person...). I am going to put everything under Public Domain, btw. I just need some time and enthusiasm.</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1205850943</time>
	    <title>Comment system</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>I have done two changes:</p>
			<ol>
				<li>commenting system - Now you can comment.</li>
				<li>XML for blog - now all my blogs are written in XML file, and read from a PHP script.</li>
			</ol>
			<p>In this process, I have learned a little bit of MySQL and XML.</p>
			<p>And by the way, addition of reCAPTCHA broke my HTML validator, so I had go for XHTML Transitional... then had to add &lt;fieldset&gt;... what a waste.</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1205335620</time>
	    <title>We’re here to devour each other alive</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/peanuts2008026112123.gif" alt="peanuts2008026112123" /><br />
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/peanuts2008073346222.gif" alt="peanuts2008073346222" /><br />
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/ch080226.gif" alt="ch080226" /><br />
			<img src="http://www.walledgardennearghat.com/images/ch080224.gif" alt="ch080224" />
			</p>
			<p>
			Peanuts: &copy; United Feature Syndicate<br />
			Calvin and Hobbes: &copy; Universal Press Syndicate
			</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1205186220</time>
	    <title>Which girl would you marry?</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>Two friends are talking:¹</p>
			<p>
			Haso: I heard you got married. Congratulations! How did you decide?<br />
			Mujo: Well, it was not easy. I had three candidates and I conducted a test. I asked the first one:<br />
			&nbsp;“What’s 2+2?”.<br />
			&nbsp;She said “4”.<br />
			&nbsp;I thought to myself, that’s good, the woman is smart.<br />
			&nbsp;The second one said, “Well, it depends. It can be 4, but sometimes it can also be 3 or 5.”<br />
			&nbsp;That’s even better, the woman is cunning.<br />
			&nbsp;I asked the third one the same question and she says, “I don’t care. Whatever my husband says, it is”.<br />
			&nbsp;I thought to myself, this woman surely will respect her husband. This is good.<br />
			Haso: So, which one did you take?<br />
			Mujo: Oh. The one with big tits, of course.<br />
			</p>
			<p style="/* text-align: right; */ font-size: small;">¹From <a href="http://ask.slashdot.org/comments.pl?sid=482032&amp;cid=22700194">http://ask.slashdot.org/comments.pl?sid=482032&amp;cid=22700194</a></p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1204845420</time>
	    <title>Finally!</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>The reasons for creating this website are two fold:</p>
			<ul type="square">
				<li>I wanted to.</li>
				<li>Now I can blog with extreme control over HTML. I love clean code!</li>
			</ul>
			<p>Even though my script may look like spaghetti, I do, at some point of time, comment them thoroughly. A look at my .zshrc will tell you that the number of lines I have edited contain more comments than code.</p>
			<p>But “clean code” is not the only reason I shelled out this (very small amount of) money! Now I can post images the way I want! I was always bothered by the way commercial blog softwares handle image. None of them are designed to give proper freedom over how images should be placed etc. Although I will miss the ready-made styles and how breezily one can change it, now at least I am away from the “group”. I am blogging on my personal website!!!</p>
			<p>Was that vanity I let spill?</p>
			<p>Ha! I always wanted to spend money wastefully without worrying about balance! :D</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1204716600</time>
    	<title>Exam</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>I think everything went fine in today’s exam.</p>
			<p>This not eating anything except fruits-thing is not working for me. Every now and then I feel hungry, and fruits are costing me more than I have a budget for.¹ I think I need to cook. I really really need to cook today.</p>
			<p>I need to go back home today.</p>
			<p style="/* text-align: right; */ font-size: small;">¹ Problems with dangling prepositions? Fuck you!!! (Or rewrite it and send me an email!)</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
    <blog>
	    <time>1204558980</time>
	    <title>The first one, the pure one, the unlearned</title>
		<text><![CDATA[
			<p>And then it happened... in a rush of moment I spent the money I would have spent on a good dinner.</p>
			<p>But all was good....</p>
			<p>... supposedly.</p>
			]]></text>
	</blog>
</blogs>
